const quizzes = [
  {
    quizName: "Basic 10 words",
    quizList: [
      {
        answer: "dog",
        question:
          "A domesticated mammal commonly kept as a pet or used for various purposes, known for its loyalty and companionship.",
      },
      {
        answer: "cat",
        question:
          "A small carnivorous mammal kept as a pet, known for its independent nature and hunting skills.",
      },
      {
        answer: "book",
        question:
          "A written or printed work consisting of pages bound together, typically containing text or images.",
      },
      {
        answer: "house",
        question:
          "A building used as a residence for individuals or families, typically providing shelter, comfort, and security.",
      },
      {
        answer: "car",
        question:
          "A four-wheeled motor vehicle used for transportation, typically powered by an internal combustion engine.",
      },
      {
        answer: "sun",
        question:
          "The star at the center of the solar system, around which Earth and other planets revolve, providing heat and light.",
      },
      {
        answer: "tree",
        question:
          "A tall, perennial plant with a trunk and branches, typically bearing leaves and producing fruits or seeds.",
      },
      {
        answer: "water",
        question:
          "A transparent, odorless, tasteless liquid that is essential for all forms of life and makes up a large part of Earth's surface.",
      },
      {
        answer: "sleep",
        question:
          "A natural state of rest for the body and mind, typically characterized by closed eyes, reduced consciousness, and relaxed muscles.",
      },
      {
        answer: "food",
        question:
          "Any nutritious substance that is eaten, drunk, or otherwise taken into the body to sustain life, provide energy, and promote growth.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    quizName: "Basic 20 words",
    quizList: [
      {
        answer: "time",
        question:
          "The indefinite continued progress of existence and events in the past, present, and future.",
      },
      {
        answer: "day",
        question:
          "A period of twenty-four hours, typically from midnight to the next midnight.",
      },
      {
        answer: "night",
        question:
          "The period of darkness between sunset and sunrise, usually when people sleep.",
      },
      {
        answer: "friend",
        question:
          "A person whom one knows and with whom one has a bond of mutual affection and trust.",
      },
      {
        answer: "money",
        question:
          "A medium of exchange in the form of coins and banknotes, used for buying goods and services.",
      },
      {
        answer: "love",
        question:
          "An intense feeling of deep affection or a strong affectionate attachment towards someone or something.",
      },
      {
        answer: "music",
        question:
          "An art form that uses sound and rhythm to express emotions and create a pleasant or meaningful experience.",
      },
      {
        answer: "school",
        question:
          "An institution for educating children or adults, providing instruction in various subjects.",
      },
      {
        answer: "work",
        question:
          "Activity involving mental or physical effort done to achieve a purpose or result.",
      },
      {
        answer: "play",
        question:
          "Engaging in activities for enjoyment and recreation, often involving games, sports, or imaginative activities.",
      },
      {
        answer: "city",
        question:
          "A large and densely populated urban area, typically the most important and economically significant place in a region or country.",
      },
      {
        answer: "country",
        question:
          "A nation with its own government, occupying a particular territory, and having distinctive cultural and political characteristics.",
      },
      {
        answer: "world",
        question:
          "The earth, together with all of its countries, peoples, and natural features.",
      },
      {
        answer: "family",
        question:
          "A group of people consisting of parents and children, living together as a unit and sharing common values and responsibilities.",
      },
      {
        answer: "job",
        question:
          "A paid position of regular employment, often involving specific duties and responsibilities.",
      },
      {
        answer: "road",
        question:
          "A wide way leading from one place to another, typically surfaced for vehicles to travel on.",
      },
      {
        answer: "game",
        question:
          "An activity or sport played according to specific rules, often for entertainment, competition, or relaxation.",
      },
      {
        answer: "name",
        question:
          "A word or set of words by which a person, animal, place, or thing is known, addressed, or referred to.",
      },
      {
        answer: "color",
        question:
          "The visual perception of different wavelengths of light, resulting in various hues and shades.",
      },
      {
        answer: "flower",
        question:
          "The reproductive structure found in plants, typically colorful and fragrant, often used for ornamental purposes.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    quizName: "Basic",
    quizList: [
      {
        answer: "Hello!",
        question: "A common greeting used to acknowledge or greet someone.",
      },
      {
        answer: "Thank you!",
        question:
          "An expression of gratitude or appreciation for something received or done.",
      },
      {
        answer: "I'm sorry.",
        question:
          "An expression used to apologize or show regret for a mistake or wrongdoing.",
      },
      {
        answer: "Excuse me.",
        question:
          "A polite phrase used to get someone's attention, ask for forgiveness, or make way through a crowded space.",
      },
      {
        answer: "How are you?",
        question:
          "A common greeting used to ask about a person's well-being or current state.",
      },
      {
        answer: "I don't understand.",
        question:
          "An expression used to indicate a lack of comprehension or confusion about something.",
      },
      {
        answer: "Nice to meet you!",
        question:
          "An expression used to convey pleasure or satisfaction upon meeting someone for the first time.",
      },
      {
        answer: "Goodbye!",
        question:
          "A parting phrase used to bid farewell or take leave of someone.",
      },
      {
        answer: "Can you help me?",
        question: "A request for assistance or support from someone.",
      },
      {
        answer: "I love you.",
        question:
          "An expression of deep affection and emotional attachment towards someone.",
      },
    ],
  },
  //! Will Delete
  {
    quizName: "Basic 10 words",
    quizList: [
      {
        answer: "dog",
        question:
          "A domesticated mammal commonly kept as a pet or used for various purposes, known for its loyalty and companionship.",
      },
      {
        answer: "cat",
        question:
          "A small carnivorous mammal kept as a pet, known for its independent nature and hunting skills.",
      },
      {
        answer: "book",
        question:
          "A written or printed work consisting of pages bound together, typically containing text or images.",
      },
      {
        answer: "house",
        question:
          "A building used as a residence for individuals or families, typically providing shelter, comfort, and security.",
      },
      {
        answer: "car",
        question:
          "A four-wheeled motor vehicle used for transportation, typically powered by an internal combustion engine.",
      },
      {
        answer: "sun",
        question:
          "The star at the center of the solar system, around which Earth and other planets revolve, providing heat and light.",
      },
      {
        answer: "tree",
        question:
          "A tall, perennial plant with a trunk and branches, typically bearing leaves and producing fruits or seeds.",
      },
      {
        answer: "water",
        question:
          "A transparent, odorless, tasteless liquid that is essential for all forms of life and makes up a large part of Earth's surface.",
      },
      {
        answer: "sleep",
        question:
          "A natural state of rest for the body and mind, typically characterized by closed eyes, reduced consciousness, and relaxed muscles.",
      },
      {
        answer: "food",
        question:
          "Any nutritious substance that is eaten, drunk, or otherwise taken into the body to sustain life, provide energy, and promote growth.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    quizName: "Basic 20 words",
    quizList: [
      {
        answer: "time",
        question:
          "The indefinite continued progress of existence and events in the past, present, and future.",
      },
      {
        answer: "day",
        question:
          "A period of twenty-four hours, typically from midnight to the next midnight.",
      },
      {
        answer: "night",
        question:
          "The period of darkness between sunset and sunrise, usually when people sleep.",
      },
      {
        answer: "friend",
        question:
          "A person whom one knows and with whom one has a bond of mutual affection and trust.",
      },
      {
        answer: "money",
        question:
          "A medium of exchange in the form of coins and banknotes, used for buying goods and services.",
      },
      {
        answer: "love",
        question:
          "An intense feeling of deep affection or a strong affectionate attachment towards someone or something.",
      },
      {
        answer: "music",
        question:
          "An art form that uses sound and rhythm to express emotions and create a pleasant or meaningful experience.",
      },
      {
        answer: "school",
        question:
          "An institution for educating children or adults, providing instruction in various subjects.",
      },
      {
        answer: "work",
        question:
          "Activity involving mental or physical effort done to achieve a purpose or result.",
      },
      {
        answer: "play",
        question:
          "Engaging in activities for enjoyment and recreation, often involving games, sports, or imaginative activities.",
      },
      {
        answer: "city",
        question:
          "A large and densely populated urban area, typically the most important and economically significant place in a region or country.",
      },
      {
        answer: "country",
        question:
          "A nation with its own government, occupying a particular territory, and having distinctive cultural and political characteristics.",
      },
      {
        answer: "world",
        question:
          "The earth, together with all of its countries, peoples, and natural features.",
      },
      {
        answer: "family",
        question:
          "A group of people consisting of parents and children, living together as a unit and sharing common values and responsibilities.",
      },
      {
        answer: "job",
        question:
          "A paid position of regular employment, often involving specific duties and responsibilities.",
      },
      {
        answer: "road",
        question:
          "A wide way leading from one place to another, typically surfaced for vehicles to travel on.",
      },
      {
        answer: "game",
        question:
          "An activity or sport played according to specific rules, often for entertainment, competition, or relaxation.",
      },
      {
        answer: "name",
        question:
          "A word or set of words by which a person, animal, place, or thing is known, addressed, or referred to.",
      },
      {
        answer: "color",
        question:
          "The visual perception of different wavelengths of light, resulting in various hues and shades.",
      },
      {
        answer: "flower",
        question:
          "The reproductive structure found in plants, typically colorful and fragrant, often used for ornamental purposes.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    quizName: "Basic",
    quizList: [
      {
        answer: "Hello!",
        question: "A common greeting used to acknowledge or greet someone.",
      },
      {
        answer: "Thank you!",
        question:
          "An expression of gratitude or appreciation for something received or done.",
      },
      {
        answer: "I'm sorry.",
        question:
          "An expression used to apologize or show regret for a mistake or wrongdoing.",
      },
      {
        answer: "Excuse me.",
        question:
          "A polite phrase used to get someone's attention, ask for forgiveness, or make way through a crowded space.",
      },
      {
        answer: "How are you?",
        question:
          "A common greeting used to ask about a person's well-being or current state.",
      },
      {
        answer: "I don't understand.",
        question:
          "An expression used to indicate a lack of comprehension or confusion about something.",
      },
      {
        answer: "Nice to meet you!",
        question:
          "An expression used to convey pleasure or satisfaction upon meeting someone for the first time.",
      },
      {
        answer: "Goodbye!",
        question:
          "A parting phrase used to bid farewell or take leave of someone.",
      },
      {
        answer: "Can you help me?",
        question: "A request for assistance or support from someone.",
      },
      {
        answer: "I love you.",
        question:
          "An expression of deep affection and emotional attachment towards someone.",
      },
    ],
  },
];

export default quizzes;
